Today's word is cloister, spelled C-L-O-I-S-T-E-R.
今天的词是“cloister”，拼写是 C-L-O-I-S-T-E-R。
Cloister is a verb. To cloister someone or something is to shut the person or thing away from the world.
“Cloister” 是一个动词。将某人或某物“cloister”掉，就是将他们或它与世隔绝。
Here's the word used in a sentence from Florida Today.
这是《今日佛罗里达》杂志中的一个例句。
Now the past Melbourne High student body president and co-valedictorian is planning to step down January 20th after serving nearly four years as NASA's administrator.
现任墨尔本高中学生会主席兼联合毕业致辞代表，在担任美国国家航空航天局（NASA）局长近四年后，计划于1月20日卸任。
My constitution is such that I'm not going to retire.
我的体质决定了我不会退休。
And what I said is, I'm going to cloister myself and write a book. And then we'll see what happens.
我说的是，我要闭关写一本书。然后我们再看情况。
Nelson, who is now 82, told reporters Wednesday during a roundtable discussion at the Kennedy Space Center Press Site.
纳尔逊（现年82岁）在周三于肯尼迪航天中心新闻发布会上与记者们举行的一场圆桌讨论会上说道。
Cloister first entered the English language as a noun in the 13th century, referring then, as it still does, to a convent or monastery.
“Cloister”一词在13世纪首次进入英语，当时它作为一个名词，指代修道院或尼姑庵，至今仍是这个意思。
More than three centuries later, English speakers began using the verb cloister to mean to seclude in or as if in a cloister.
三个多世纪后，英语使用者开始使用动词“cloister”来表示将某人隔离在修道院内或如同隔离在修道院内。
Today, the noun can also refer to the monastic life or to a covered and usually arched passage along or around a court.
如今，这个名词还可以指代修道院生活，或者指围绕庭院或沿着庭院建造的带顶的、通常是拱形的通道。
You may also encounter the adjective cloistered with the meaning separated from the rest of the world as if in a cloister, as in she leads a private cloistered life in the country.
你可能还会遇到形容词“cloistered”，意思是与世隔绝，如同在修道院中一样，例如“她在乡下过着私密隐居的生活”。
Cloister ultimately comes from the Latin verb claudere, meaning to close.
回廊最终源自拉丁语动词 claudere，意为“关闭”。
Other words that can be traced back to the prolific claudere root include close, conclude, exclude, include, preclude, seclude and recluse.
其他可以追溯到多产的“claudere”词根的词包括 close（关闭）、conclude（结论）、exclude（排除）、include（包含）、preclude（阻止）、seclude（隔绝）和 recluse（隐士）。